Welcome to Kanani Kamal channel friends. In this video we are going to look at
10 file formats.
The file formats
are classified into
two categories. The first
category is the text file format. The text file formats are five different types
you can see that here starting with PDF
subtitles Excel JSON and finally CSV. On the right side of this page we can see
the multimedia file formats like WAV MP3 PNG SVG and finally JPEG.
The points we have to be aware is that this tail this 10 file formats have a huge amount of impact
when we work with the artificial intelligence models. We have to understand that the models
read just numbers. Irrespective of whatever format we see here whether it is a CSV or
whether it is a WAV the model is going to see only the bytes. The file patterns and the
structures are going to decide how the model looks at the file. The structures and the patterns are
useful for us to see the file and its contents but the model and the programming languages like Python
really don't care about how the structures are.
Accessları orders. If you delimấp a bit transfer there are still only there are still
properties. Thanks for theарised batteries.